<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Creative Craft</title>
    <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Creative Craft</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:23:59 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:39987/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Tea Coaster</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/teac-coaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/teac-coaster/</guid>
      <description>Indulge in the perfect blend of tradition and contemporary flair with our Crochet Tea Coasters. Each coaster is meticulously handcrafted with a sturdy MDF base, ensuring durability and stability. The intricate crochet work adds a touch of artisanal charm, creating a cozy ambiance for your tea moments.&#xA;Crafted with love and attention to detail, these coasters are not just practical accessories but also exquisite pieces of art. The combination of MDF and crochet creates a unique texture that enhances the visual appeal of your table setting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resin Bookmark</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/resin-bookmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/resin-bookmark/</guid>
      <description>Introducing our exquisite Resin Bookmark featuring the sacred Arabic phrase &amp;ldquo;Bismillah&amp;rdquo; (بسم الله الرحمن الرحيم), meaning &amp;ldquo;In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.&amp;rdquo; Crafted with precision and infused with artistic flair, this unique piece serves not only as a practical companion for your literary adventures but also as a spiritual reminder.&#xA;Each stroke of resin intricately captures the beauty of Arabic calligraphy, transforming the bookmark into a mesmerizing work of art.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Resin Keychain: Personalized Letter &#39;M&#39; with &#39;Z&#39; Accent in Red and White</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/letterm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:44:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/letterm/</guid>
      <description>Introducing our captivating Resin Keychain, a personalized masterpiece crafted with meticulous attention to detail. Inspired by the beauty of individuality, this keychain features the letter &amp;ldquo;M&amp;rdquo; adorned with a charming miniaturized &amp;ldquo;z,&amp;rdquo; delicately encapsulated in a vibrant blend of red and white resin.&#xA;Each keychain is a testament to the fusion of artistry and functionality, where the bold lines of the letter &amp;ldquo;M&amp;rdquo; are complemented by the intricate detailing of the smaller &amp;ldquo;z,&amp;rdquo; creating a visually stunning interplay of shapes and colors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resin Set</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/resin-coaster-bookmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/resin-coaster-bookmark/</guid>
      <description>Introducing our exquisite Resin Set of 3 – a captivating ensemble that seamlessly blends functionality with artistic elegance. This meticulously crafted collection features a set of two stunning pieces: a 4-inch tea coaster and a 3.5-inch bookmark, both adorned with enchanting resin designs.&#xA;Elevate your tea time experience with the intricately designed 4-inch tea coaster, where functionality meets beauty in perfect harmony. Each sip becomes a moment of indulgence as you place your cup upon this uniquely crafted coaster, adding a touch of sophistication to your daily rituals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letter &#39;J&#39; with Sweetheart Accent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/letterj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:50:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/letterj/</guid>
      <description>Introducing our delightful Resin Keychain featuring the Letter &amp;lsquo;J&amp;rsquo; adorned with a miniature resin heart, a heartfelt symbol of love and affection. Crafted with precision and infused with artistic flair, this charming keychain is a perfect blend of elegance and sentimentality.&#xA;Each keychain is meticulously handcrafted, ensuring attention to detail and durability. The bold silhouette of the Letter &amp;lsquo;J&amp;rsquo; is accentuated by the delicate presence of the resin heart, creating a visually striking and meaningful piece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Resin Name Art</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/resin-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/resin-name/</guid>
      <description>Immerse yourself in the enchanting world of personalized resin art with our captivating creations. Each piece is a testament to meticulous craftsmanship, expertly capturing the essence of your chosen name in a stunning array of vibrant colors and textures. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s commemorating a cherished family name, celebrating a newborn&amp;rsquo;s arrival, or conveying a heartfelt message to a loved one, our personalized resin art serves as a timeless keepsake that transcends the ordinary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Letter &#39;A&#39; with Custom Name &#39;Abdeli&#39; in Sea Green</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/letterabdeli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:56:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/letterabdeli/</guid>
      <description>Introducing our exquisite Personalized Resin Keychain, featuring the distinguished Letter &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; adorned with a bespoke touch—a miniature keychain bearing the name &amp;lsquo;Abdeli,&amp;rsquo; delicately crafted in a soothing sea green hue.&#xA;Each keychain is meticulously handcrafted, blending precision with artistry to create a unique accessory that exudes charm and individuality. The bold presence of the Letter &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; is beautifully complemented by the personalized detail of the name &amp;lsquo;Abdeli,&amp;rsquo; adding a touch of sentimentality to every journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chic Crocheted Clutch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/chich-crocheted-purd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/chich-crocheted-purd/</guid>
      <description>Behold our exquisite Crocheted Clutch Bag, where timeless sophistication meets artisanal craftsmanship in perfect harmony. Crafted with meticulous attention to detail, this clutch is a true testament to the artistry of handwork.&#xA;Each carefully woven stitch of the crocheted pattern reflects the dedication and skill of our artisans, resulting in a beautifully textured exterior that captivates both the eye and the touch. Adorned with a whimsical tassel accent, this clutch exudes charm and personality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Textured Knit Purse: A Unique Blend of Yarn and Acrylic </title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/acrylic-purse-crochet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/acrylic-purse-crochet/</guid>
      <description>Immerse yourself in the distinctive charm of our Handcrafted Yarn and Acrylic Purse, where eco-friendly materials meet artisanal craftsmanship to create a truly unique accessory. Meticulously crafted with a blend of yarn and acrylic, this purse embodies a commitment to both style and sustainability, offering a guilt-free indulgence in fashion.&#xA;The intricate knit pattern of this purse adds depth and character, showcasing the exquisite artistry of our skilled artisans. Each stitch tells a story of dedication and creativity, while the bold color combinations infuse the design with vibrancy and personality, ensuring that it stands out in any crowd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tassel Temptation Round Purse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/tesel-temptaion-round-purse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:02:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/tesel-temptaion-round-purse/</guid>
      <description>Immerse yourself in the epitome of understated elegance with our Compact Round Yarn Purse, a delightful accessory designed for the modern trendsetter. Crafted with the utmost precision and care, this purse boasts a sleek and compact round design, making it the perfect companion for your on-the-go lifestyle. Its minimalist silhouette exudes sophistication, while the soft and supple yarn construction adds a touch of artisanal charm, elevating it beyond the ordinary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whimsical Chain Crochet Clutch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/whimsical-crochet-purse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/whimsical-crochet-purse/</guid>
      <description>Handcrafted with precision and care, this purse is a testament to the timeless artistry of crochet.&#xA;Every stitch of the yarn is lovingly woven to create a luxurious textured exterior that exudes charm and sophistication. The delicate chain detail adds a touch of refinement, elevating the purse&amp;rsquo;s style to new heights while providing a hint of glamour.&#xA;Perfect for adding a touch of handmade charm to any ensemble, this crochet purse is as practical as it is stylish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stitched in Love: Personalized Wedding Invitation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/work11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 20:23:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:39987/portfolio/work11/</guid>
      <description>Celebrate the union of two hearts with our exquisite wedding invitation, meticulously crafted as a cross-stitched picture of the happy couple against the backdrop of their special day marked on a calendar. Each stitch is woven with love and care, capturing the essence of the couple&amp;rsquo;s bond and the joyous occasion they are inviting you to share.&#xA;This personalized masterpiece isn&amp;rsquo;t just an invitation; it&amp;rsquo;s a work of art that symbolizes the love and commitment between the couple.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
